7 hours ago
How come Drones would pass by without doing anything?
This doesn't make sense.
This isn't a setup, is it? LOL
They said they couldn't read his Psycho-Pass because he was wearing a helmet.
Whoooooooooa!
Street scanners are pointless!
It's sad that this is happening for real.
You moron. This isn't real. LOL
This is bad. Seriously, the Area Stress Level must be getting to its limit.
I'm so scared that I can't go out!
You moron! This isn't real. LOL
There's no murders in this world, right? LOL
This has to be the MWPSB's doing.
Calling the Drones in didn't work, right?
The end of the week has begun!
No, it's the end of the world that began. LOL
Helmet, pleaaaaaaaaase!!
I got a call from my employer.
What did they say?
They said that it's temporarily closed so I should try not to go out.
If we go out, we'll be killed.
What if the Psycho-Pass validation at the entrance doesn't work...
The Psycho-Pass validation should work, shouldn't it?
Does this mean that it's dangerous no matter where you are?
It's better not to look outside. If they notice you're there, you might get killed.
If you have that kind of time, make a weapon.
Give me your portable
terminals and credit cards.
携帯端末とクレジットカードをよこせ
And tell me the password.
パスワードを教えろ
If you see someone wearing a helmet, be cautious.
Run! Run! Run! Run! Run! Run!
What do I do?
If their Crime Coefficient is unknown, it's pointless to call the police, right?
Is that friend of yours okay? Isn't he in danger?
I don't know... I can't reach him.
I want some ideas about everyday stuff that would work as a weapon.
If you hold the stalk of a houseplant and swing it around, that can be a weapon, right?
Put something heavy in a sock.
Huh? A houseplant is...
Stop! Stop it!
やめろ！やめてくれ！
Please stop, I'm begging...
本当に　やめて…
Grandpas and Grandmas still keep
money under their mattress, right?
おじいちゃん おばあちゃんって
いまだにタンス預金とかやってるんでしょ？
I saw it on the news.
ニュースで見たよ
It's convenient since it can be made
electronic without laundering, isn't it?
そういうのロンダリングなしで電子化できて 便利だよね
We don't have
things like that in this house.
そんなもの… ないよ この家には…
I would like to show
Cut open my skull
Look into my head
I don't know why I'm so harsh
I could be so brash
I'm going to clash
'Cause I feel
I can always show
my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear
Lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all again
'Cause I feel
I can always show
my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear
Lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all
So it goes again
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 知音   校对:西西   时间轴:葛蔓 压制：娜夏
#15 The Town Where
Sulfur Falls
So, today, we've gathered all
the top honor students...
という訳で今日は同期でもトップクラスの優等生諸君に
...who started in the same year.
集まっていただきました
Don't you think it's totally unfair?
めちゃくちゃ不公平だと思いません？
You guys have promising futures.
前途有望な君たち
As for us, we know before we even
try that we're gonna fail at everything.
それに対してやる前から何もかも駄目だって分かってる俺たち
何でこんな…
Why are you doing this?
Stop it... This is terrible.
やめて…ひどい…
What's terrible is not us,
but the Sibyl System.
ひどいのは俺たちじゃなくてシビュラシステムだよ
Based on Sibyl's Judgment, we know
that we no longer can get a decent job.
シビュラの判定で
俺たちはもうろくな仕事に就けないことは分かってる
A life with no hope for the future...
将来に何の期待もない人生なんてさ
Since you guys are blessed by the system,
you wouldn't get it, would you?!
システムに祝福されてるお前らには分かんないだろ
What's your problem?!
何なんだよもう
We saw you take one
of those helmets off earlier.
さっき　あんたがヘルメット脱ぐのを見たんだよ
Huh?
You caused all sorts of chaos,
and now you just take that helmet off
散々暴れておいて ヘルメットを脱いだだけで知らんぷり決め込もうとは
and act as if you knew nothing about it...
Isn't that a little cruel?
ちょっとひどいんじゃないか
You've got the wrong idea!
勘違いしてる　あんたら
If you really think that,
why don't you check my Hu...
そういうなら俺の色相を…
Because of you helmet people,
the Area Stress Level is rising.
お前らヘルメットのせいで エリアストレスが上昇してるんだ
For God's sake,
don't drag us into this whole thing!
頼むから巻き込まないでくれよ
Our Crime Coefficients
wouldn't go up, would they?
私たちの犯罪係数が上がったりしませんよね
I saw something on the net earlier
さっきネットで見ました
that said if it's for self-defense
or if the one you hurt is a criminal,
正当防衛だったり
相手が犯罪者なら むしろ犯罪係数は下降するそうです
your Crime Coefficient would
go down instead.
It's chaos outside.
Call the MWPSB.
What is the MWPSB doing?!
Stay inside and hide.
Failed to escape...
What're they gonna do if they even drag people who have nothing to do with them into it?!
They're trash who won't contribute anything to society anyway.
Aren't there latent criminals mixed in with them?
You guys' Hues have already been clouded, haven't they?
The ones wearing helmets aren't the only criminals.
It's too late.
If those helmet people are killed, things will be peaceful again, right?
Self-defense. Self-defense. Self-defense...
No, no, no, no...
Do you hear yourself?
It's not too late. We should do it with our own hands.
Isn't that risky?
It's better than doing nothing.
Several dozen cases...
数十件…
No, several hundred cases!
The number keeps growing!
いや　数百件 まだ増えてる
The brutality is
spreading like a contagion...
凶暴性の伝染
The psycho-hazard has gotten this big?
サイコハザードがここまで大規模に…
It's more than that.
At this point, it's turned into a riot.
そんなお上品なもんじゃない
ここまでくりゃ暴動だ
The Area Stress Level
is rising like crazy, too.
エリアストレス上昇もえらいことになってる
It's not just helmet people
who're going on a rampage.
Aren't they latent criminals from the start?
Scared citizens are committing mass violence all over the place.
暴れてるのはヘルメットの連中だけじゃない
It's not just helmet people
who're going on a rampage.
おびえた市民があっちこっちで集団暴行を引き起こしている
Must be a psycho-hazard...
It's begun...
It's not just helmet people
who're going on a rampage.
Someone without a helmet is going on a rampage?!
Run! Run! Run! Run! Run! Run!
Chief Kasei issued
an emergency summons.
禾生局長より緊急招集だ
She's ordering all CID personnel to
report for duty, including those off duty.
非番の人員も含め 刑事課に総動員指令が下った
You feel restless?
落ち着かないかね
Yeah, of course. This situation
would make one feel uneasy.
そりゃね
不安にもなりますよ
What's awaiting us from here on out?
果たしてここから先に何が待っているのか
What will happen to this town?
この街がどうなってしまうのか
I really like that ordinary side of yours.
君のそういう普通なところ すごくいいと思う
僕も君も　ごく普通で本質的にありきたりな人間だ
You and I are both quite
ordinary and essentially common.
I've never thought of
myself as an avaricious person.
自分のことを欲張りだと思ったことはないよ
A world in which everyday things
are done in an everyday way...
当たり前のことが 当たり前に行われる世界
I just like things like that, that's all.
僕は そういうのが好きなだけでね
We're quite ordinary and common...
ごく普通でありきたりなわれわれが 普通でない街に犯罪を仕掛ける
...and we're starting a crime
in a town that is not ordinary...
A town that is not ordinary, huh?
「普通でない街」か…
How should I put it?
何だろうな…
This town is like a parody of
one of the novels I read in the past.
昔読んだ小説のパロディーみたいだ　この街は…
Like... the ones by William Gibson?
例えば…ウィリアム·ギブスンですか
More like Philip K. Dick, perhaps.
フィリップ·Ｋ·ディックかな
It's not as controlling as the
society George Orwell depicted,
ジョージ·オーウェルが描く社会ほど支配的でなく
and it's not as wild
as what Gibson depicted.
ギブスンが描くほどワイルドでもない
I've never read Dick.
ディック 読んだことないな…
最初に１冊読むなら何がいいでしょう
What book would you
recommend I read first?
『アンドロイドは電気羊の夢を見るか？』
Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?
That's the original story
of an old movie, right?
古い映画の原作ですね
だいぶ内容が違う
The content is quite different.
いつか暇なときに比較してみるといい
You should compare them
when you have time some day.
ダウンロードしておきます
I'll go ahead and download it.
Why don't you buy paper books?
E-books lack character.
紙の本を買いなよ 電子書籍は味気ない
Is that right?
そういうもんですかね
本はね ただ文字を読むんじゃない
Books are not something
that you just read words in.
自分の感覚を調整するためのツールでもある
They're also a tool to adjust your senses.
Adjust?
調整？
When I'm not feeling well, there are times
that I can't take in what I read.
調子の悪いときに本の内容が頭に入ってこないことがある
そういうときは何が読書の邪魔をしているか考える
When that happens, I try to think about
what could be hindering my reading.
調子が悪いときでも　すらすらと内容が入ってくる本もある
There are also books that I can take in
smoothly even when I'm not feeling well.
I try to think why.
なぜそうなのか考える
It might be something like mental tuning.
精神的な調律 チューニングみたいなものかな
調律する際大事なのは
What's important when you tune is
紙に指で触れている感覚や
the feeling of the paper that
you're touching with your fingers
and the momentary stimulation
your brain receives when you turn pages.
本をぺらぺらめくったとき 瞬間的に脳の神経を刺激するものだ
I feel kinda discouraged.
何だかへこむな…
Hm?
When I talk with you,
あなたと話していると
俺の今までの人生　ずっと損をしてたような気分になる
I feel like I've been missing
out on something all my life.
You're reading too much into it.
考え過ぎだね
ですかね
Maybe.
It's about time.
そろそろ時間だ
Shall we go?
行きますか
This is just a random thought, but...
どうでもいいんだけどさ
Yes?
はい？
It's too good to be true that
an outstanding hacker likes Gibson.
すご腕のハッカーがギブスン好きってのは でき過ぎだな
The Metropolitan area is currently
facing an unprecedented crisis.
目下　首都圏は未曽有の危機に直面している
Ever since the Sibyl System was introduced,
シビュラシステムの導入以来
people believed it had eliminated
the possibility of citizens rioting.
市民の暴動は　可能性として廃絶されたものと判断されたため
So the current MWPSB has neither
現在の公安局には　暴徒の鎮圧に備えた人員も装備もない
personnel nor equipment that
are prepared to suppress a mob.
あまりにも平和が長過ぎた
We've had peace too long.
We're currently working to switch
the parts on the border security Drones
現在国境警備ドローンの装備を
非殺傷兵器に換装する作業が急ピッチで進められているが
with non-lethal weapons at a quick pace,
but the situation out
there requires prompt action.
現場の状況は一刻を争う
Until a full-fledged
suppression unit is formed,
本格的な鎮圧部隊の編成が整うまでの間
we have no choice but
to have those of you at the CID
諸君ら刑事課のメンバーに
市民の安全を守る最後の盾となってもらうしかない
act as the last remaining
shield to keep our citizens safe.
The cymatic scan
blocking helmets in question
問題のサイマティックスキャン妨害ヘルメットは
ドミネーターの機能を阻害する
hinder the functionality of the Dominators.
これに対して最も有効なスタンバトンで対処してもらう
To deal with them, use stun batons,
the most effective weapon against them.
相手が大人数の場合は
In case you're dealing with a crowd,
I'll permit the use of emergency
electromagnetic pulse grenades.
緊急用の電磁パルスグレネードの使用を許可する
サージ電流によりヘルメットが無力化されれば
Once the helmet becomes
incapacitated by the surge current,
the usual enforcement actions
by Dominators become possible.
従来どおりドミネーターによる執行が可能になる
ただし グレネードの使用についてはくれぐれも慎重に配慮すること
However, make sure you pay careful
attention when you use the grenades.
うかつな場所で電磁パルスを発生させれば
If the electromagnetic pulse
is generated in the wrong place,
city functions could be disabled, too.
都市機能のまひもあり得る
How many grenades are available?
グレネードの数はどれくらいでしょう
There are not many.
多くはない
There are probably just enough to
give two grenades to each person here.
ここにいる全員に１人２個ずつで品切れだろう
Assemble into teams of three.
３人で１チームつくってもらう
Assign each team an area and
suppress the riots one by one.
そしてエリアを分担してあとはしらみつぶしで鎮圧だ
It'll be time-consuming and dangerous,
but we don't have any other choice.
時間がかかるし　危険も伴うが
他に方法はない
This town's future is at stake.
この街の未来が懸かっている
I'm counting on you guys.
よろしく頼む
あなたと一緒に歩くのが危ない橋だって自覚はあった
I was aware that the path I was
about to walk with you was dangerous.
But you didn't feel like going back...
でも　引き返す気にはなれなかった
That's because I thought
the Sibyl System was strange.
だって変ですもん シビュラシステムって
Those who are perfectly happy
entrusting everything in their lives
あんな訳の分かんないものに生活の全てを預けて
to some nonsense like
that are the ones who're crazy.
平気な連中の方がどうかしている
俺は外国人ですからね
I'm a foreigner... so I appreciate
simply being able to live in this country.
この国で暮らしていけるだけでも感謝 と言いたいところなんですが
Well, so I'd like to say...
槙島さんの言ったとおりですよ
...but it's just like you said, Mr. Makishima.
当たり前のことを当たり前にできるように…
For us to be able to do everyday
things in an everyday way...
僕にとっては生まれ育った街だ
To me, this is the town
I was born and raised in.
It's a pressing problem.
切実な問題だよ
こいつらはあなたが行う破壊の先を見たがっている連中です
These guys want to see what lies
beyond the destruction you'll cause.
「破壊の先」か…
Beyond the destruction, huh?
先があればよし
If there's something beyond it, that's good.
If there isn't, then I'll accept it.
なければ それはそれで受け入れる
How's the information
manipulation on the net going?
ネットでの情報操作は
The AI I set up beforehand is already at work.
事前に仕掛けたＡＩがもう活動中です
Shogo Makishima...
He's really done it this time.
やってくれるぜ　槙島聖護
Hold on a sec.
でも　待ってください
We still haven't
found conclusive evidence
このヘルメット犯罪に槙島が関与しているという決定的な証拠は
that shows that Makishima has
something to do with this helmet crime.
まだ見つかっていません
Think about it.
考えてみろ　普通の人間は
The moment an ordinary person
thinks of making equipment
シビュラシステムを無効化する装備を作ってみようと思った時点で
that makes the Sibyl System invalid,
their Hue would get clouded.
色相が濁る
それを設計し 量産し ばらまいた
But this guy designed it,
mass produced it, and distributed it.
下準備には数カ月はかかっているだろう
It probably took him at least
several months to prepare for it.
部品の発注　流通の手配
Ordering parts,
arranging for circulation...
You can't do those things while
avoiding the scanners throughout town.
街じゅうのスキャナーを避けながらできることじゃない
あのヘルメットを作れるのは
Only someone who can confront the
Sibyl System without wearing the helmet
ヘルメットなしにシビュラシステムに対抗できる人間だけだ
can make that helmet.
A mass psycho-hazard that
takes advantage of a blind spot
シビュラシステムの盲点を突いた
in the Sibyl System...
集団サイコハザード
それが槙島の目的ってこと
So that's Makishima's goal?
違う…
No...
What?
Because it seemed
だって　槙島の犯罪は
he was always trying to
find answers through his crimes.
いつだって何か答えを探すようなところがあった
This is a terrible riot, but it's hard
to think that this chaos is his only goal.
ひどい暴動だけど
この混乱だけが目的とは思えない
I agree with you, Inspector.
監視官に賛成だ
If he was a criminal who'd find
enjoyment in watching a riot like this,
こんな暴動を見物して喜ぶ程度の犯罪者だったなら
もっと楽に逮捕できる
we could arrest him more easily.
Whoa! Things are terrible on the net, too.
ネット上もひどいな
From false rumors to true information...
A lot is flying back and forth.
デマからマブネタまで大量に飛び交ってる
When the media coverage
should be restrained!
報道規制はかかってるはずなのに…
False rumors stand out more.
デマの方が目立つな
What is this?!
"The MWPSB kills all the residents"?!
何だよ
「公安局が住民皆殺し」って
We have to stop them!
止めなきゃ
このまま突っ込んで何人かひき殺しちゃいなよ
Why don't you run over and kill some
of them by driving straight into them?
No way!
やですよ
I thought it was a good idea.
俺グッドアイデアだと思ったけど
How was that a good idea?!
どこがですか
厚生省公安局です
This is the MWPSB!
Stop this violence immediately
直ちに暴力行為をやめて
and lay on your stomach
with your hands behind your head!
腕を頭の上で組んで地面に伏せなさい
We have no choice but to resort to force.
実力行使しかないな
Give them a warning again!
もう一度警告だ
This is the MWPSB!
こちらは厚生省公安局です
If you don't stop this violence,
we'll use the Dominators!
これ以上暴力行為を停止しない場合は
ドミネーターを使用します
Depending on your Crime Coefficient,
you could lose your life!
犯罪係数によっては命を失うことになります
I repeat! Lay on your stomach
with your hands behind your head!
繰り返します
腕を頭の上で組んで地面に伏せなさい
Why are you doing this?!
The helmet people are the bad ones!
何だよ　悪いのはヘルメットの連中じゃないか
You guys at the MWPSB
公安局は大量に出回ってるヘルメットの方を何とかしろよ
should do something about the tons
of helmets that have been distributed!
We're the victims, aren't we?!
俺たちは被害者だろ
Shut up! That's one thing,
but this is another!
うるせえな
それはそれ　これはこれ
What's the matter?
どうしたんですか
These guys are victims, too.
こいつらも被害者だ
True...
確かに 犯罪に巻き込まれなければ 市民の暴徒化なんて…
If they weren't dragged into this,
the citizens wouldn't have become violent.
No, I mean the helmet people.
違う　ヘルメットの方だ
今やったように 時間はかかるが
Just like what just happened,
although it'll take time,
the helmet people will eventually
all be hunted and killed.
いずれヘルメット着用者は全員狩り殺される
Even if we didn't get them, the citizens
will gang up on them and beat them up.
俺たちがやらなくても市民がリンチにかける
さっきちょっと気になったんだ
I got a little worried about this earlier,
but the false rumors on
the net are rather offensive.
ネット上のデマが攻撃的な方向に偏っている
If this was one way that
Makishima's manipulating information...
これが槙島の情報操作の一環だとしたら…
Either he himself or his partner in crime...
やつ自身か それともやつの仲間か…
どちらかがすご腕のクラッカーなのはもう分かってる
We already know that one of
the two is an outstanding cracker.
All those crimes wouldn't be
possible if that wasn't the case.
そうじゃなきゃできない犯罪ばかりだった
Look at the faces of those who
just surrendered and took off the helmets.
今投降してヘルメットを脱いだ連中の顔を見てみろよ
They're trash who can't
commit a crime without the helmet.
ヘルメットがなけりゃ何の犯罪もできないクズどもだ
In a sense, they were just
playing into Makishima's hands.
ある意味　槙島の手のひらの上で踊っていただけさ
Hold on a sec. If that's the case,
then Makishima's goal is...
ちょい待ち ってことは　槙島の狙いは…
Suppose that everything
is going as he planned.
全てがやつの筋書きどおりだったと仮定する
If even what we're doing this
very moment is what he expected...
今俺たちがやってることさえやつの思うつぼだとしたら…
Inspector, what are the riot locations
that we were asked to suppress first?
監視官　まず優先対象として鎮圧要請のあった暴動箇所は
Let's see...
えっと…
ここです
Here they are.
What comes to mind here is a feint.
考えられるのは陽動だ
What if this whole thing was
pre-arranged so that the riots would
これが全て刑事課の人員をおびき寄せるためだけに
intensify at those places just to
lure the detectives at the CID out...
あらかじめ暴動が激化するように仕組まれたポイントだとしたら…
This is... Don't tell me!
これは…まさか
These past five years,
この５年間
I've been frantically trying to
grasp the truth of the Sibyl System.
俺はシビュラシステムの実態をつかむために 血眼になってきました
首都圏各地に設置されたサーバーによる分散型並列処理
Distributed parallel processing
by servers installed at various
locations in the Metropolitan area...
鉄壁のフォールトトレラントを実現した理想のシステム
An ideal system that made
iron-clad fault tolerance a reality...
Those are the catchphrases
used by the Ministry of Welfare.
それが厚生省のうたい文句です
Well, if they want to measure and analyze
まあ実際 全国民のサイコパスを測定し分析するともなれば
the Psycho-Pass
of every citizen of this country,
it actually requires
a great deal of computation.
膨大な演算が必要になる
Naturally, that's not possible
当然　ネットワークを経由したグリッドコンピューティングい
unless they do grid computing
or something over the network.
でもしないかぎり追い付かな
But then, the more I tried to investigate it,
ところがね　検証すればするほど
the more I realized that the
flow of data was clearly strange.
データの流れ方が明らかにおかしい
街じゅうのスキャナー  公認カウンセリングＡＩ
Scanners throughout town, authorized
counseling AIs, and the Dominators...
そして　ドミネーター
一見グリッドを巡り巡っているかのように見えたデータが
At first glance, the data appeared
to be transferred throughout the grid,
but it was actually just being
passed from one place to another.
実は全てたらい回しにされてるだけだった
Then, I finally noticed...
そこでようやく気付いたんです
...that there's a single relay
point that every communication
シビュラを巡る全ての通信が必ず一度は経由する中継点が
in the Sibyl System goes through
at least once without exception.
ただ１カ所だけ存在することに
もしそこに誰も知らないスタンドアローンのシステムが隠されてて
If a stand-alone system that
no one knows about is hidden there
and that one machine is managing
all of Sibyl's processing and computation,
全てのシビュラの処理演算をそいつ１機が賄っているのだとしたら…
everything makes sense.
全て辻褄が合うんです
やはり君は天才だね
As I thought, you're a genius.
まあ不可解なのはその性能ですよ
Well, what's mysterious is its capacity.
If it's really a stand-alone system,
it means that it's exhibiting
もし孤立したシステムだとすると
そいつは既存の技術では説明のつかないスループットを発揮していることになる
a throughput that is not
possible with existing technologies.
It makes no sense to put
it all in one place to start with.
そもそも１カ所に集約している意味が分からない
When you think about the security risk,
保安上のリスクを考えればどう考えても危険過ぎる
it's too risky no
matter how you look at it.
あるいはあえて危険を冒してまで 秘匿性を保ちたいのだとしたら
Or, what if they want to keep it secret
even if they have to take a risk for it?
Exactly.
そういうこと
When it's that suspicious,
I just have to find out...
ここまでうさんくさいとなるとね
もう確かめなきゃ気が済まなくなりますよ
...the true nature
of the Sibyl System.
シビュラシステムの正体ってやつを…
And, you tracked it back to this facility?
そして 君が確かめた問題の施設がここか
This is the relay point for the
various data collected by cymatic scans.
サイマティックスキャンで収集されたあらゆるデータの中継点
Plus, there are clear traces of the power
consumption in this area being faked.
おまけにこのエリアの消費電力 明らかに偽装されてる形跡があります
It's almost certain that the
Sibyl System is inside of this building,
ほぼ間違いなくシビュラシステムはこの厚生省ノナタワーの中にある
the Ministry of Welfare's Nona Tower.
さあ　それでは諸君
Well then, guys...
...why don't we uncover the
heart of the Great Prophetess?
ひとつ暴き出してやろうじゃないか
偉大なる神託の巫女のはらわたを…
Mr. Ginoza!
宜野座さん　首謀者の目的は厚生省ノナタワーの襲撃です
The ringleader's goal is to attack
the Ministry of Welfare's Nona Tower!
暴動は全ておとりなんです
The riots are all decoys!
Don't be ridiculous!
バカな そんな根拠のない臆測で持ち場を離れるな
Don't leave your post based on
groundless speculation!
People's lives are at stake!
こっちは人命が懸かってるんだぞ
でも　監視官も執行官も全て出払った中央区の官庁街はもぬけの殻ですよ
But since all the Inspectors
and Enforcers are out on the field,
the government district
in Chuo Ward is empty!
In their hands, guard Drones
are as good as scarecrows!
あいつらの手に掛かったら
警備ドローンなんてカカシも同然です
If we do nothing and fall behind,
このまま後手に回っていたら
the situation will be
irreversible this time for sure!
今度こそ取り返しのつかない事態になります
Please let us go, at least!
せめて　私たちだけでも
分かった
Okay!
You guys go there first
and check the situation!
まずは君たちが先行して状況を確認しろ
こちらは引き続き各地の鎮圧を続行する
We'll continue to suppress
the riot in each area.
何かあったら　すぐ　連絡を
If something is up,
let me know immediately!
Okay!
はい
It's come into our sight.
見えてきたぜ
There's no way that I could love someone
But I want someone to love me
Even if yesterday could
continue unchanging into forever
You and I would never get anywhere
God... where did you go?
I don't hear any response,
but that's how it always is
Are you still here?
You'll never walk alone
I'll go with you
No matter the sin,
I'll bear the burden for you
I'll walk an uncharted path
All alone with you
A world where humans' state of mind and the tendency of their
personalities can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations
are recorded and policed, these measured numbers
used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass."
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in the show
are fictitious and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.